gleemax.com 2014-05-30

# Privacy | company.wizards.com

_Last modified October 8, 2013._

**Table of Contents**

[](http://www.esrb.org/confirm/wizards-confirmation.jsp) Welcome  
What does the Privacy Policy apply to?  
What information does Wizards collect?  
Chat, Forums, Blogs, and Discussion Lists  
Online Stores  
Promotions  
E-mail  
Web Postcards  
Resumes  
Online Surveys  
Who is collecting my information and how will it be used?  
With whom does Wizards share my personal information?  
Social Media  
International Transfer of Information?  
Clear GIFs, Cookies and IP Addresses  
Log Files  
Linking to third party sites  
Opt-out  
Safeguarding your personal information  
Review, update, and removal of personal information  
Your California Privacy Rights  
Questions and Complaints  
Note to Parents  
Teenages (Ages 13-17)  
Children Under 13  
Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information  
Disclosure of Children's Personal Information  
Safeguarding Children's Personal Information  
Notification of Updates to the Privacy Policy  
Parental Access  
Wizards Contact Information  

###  WELCOME!

Wizards of the Coast web sites bring you the coolest information about the world of hobby gaming … Wizards of the Coast web sites bring you the latest about the world of hobby gaming, a place to meet and play with other gamers like you, and discover some of the best independent and strategy games available. If you are a parent or guardian and are interested in knowing more about Wizards’ policy regarding the online collection of information from children, we recommend reviewing the Note To Parents below.

Wizards respects the privacy rights of its online visitors and is committed to providing you with a secure online environment. We have adopted an Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide us online.

This Privacy Statement and the certification seal located to your right confirms that Wizards is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board’s Privacy Online Program: ESRB Privacy Online. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all our web sites have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Online to meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our sites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by ESRB.

Whenever you visit a web site that displays the ESRB Privacy Online certification seal, you can expect to be notified of:

  * Exactly what personal information may be collected;
  * The consequences, if any, resulting from your refusal to provide personal information;
  * Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information;
  * How this information may be used, including, with whom, if anyone, it might be shared;
  * Whether a company uses cookies or tracks IP Addresses to collect information;
  * What choices you have with regard to the use of your personal information;
  * How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity;
  * How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company collects and maintains;
  * Where and how to ask questions or file complaints; and,
  * Whether and how information is collected from Children under 13.

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact the Privacy Policy Administrator.

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

For complaints, you can also contact ESRB Privacy Online directly through their [consumer hotline](http://www.esrb.org/privacy), or by regular mail at 317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor, New York, NY 10017.

Back to top

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**

This privacy policy applies to all web sites operated or controlled by Wizards including [www.wizards.com](http://www.wizards.com/) (collectively, all such websites shall be referred to as the "Sites"). This privacy policy does not pertain to information that is collected offline. BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO OUR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES STATED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITES.

Back to top

**What information does Wizards collect?**

Wizards wants to give you the most exciting Internet experience possible. To help us figure out what you like and don't like about our sites, we may ask for your opinion from time to time. Wizards may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you:

create a profile to participate in Wizards community features 
  * shop at one of our affiliate online stores
  * give credit card information to make purchases from our Sites*
  * enter a shipping and billing address when making a purchase
  * participate in contests, events, or promotions
  * send questions or comments to Wizards customer service
  * submit your resume to us online
  * fill out online surveys

*While Wizards may collect credit card data from its customers from time to time, it will also use third party credit card processing companies to process your payment transactions. When it is using such a third party processing company, Wizards will not have access to your credit card data.

The requested information may include personal information such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, and home address. In addition, we may request demographic information such as your age, the gender and birth dates of children in your household, and toy and game ownership and preferences.

If you are under the age of 13, some features of the Sites may be unavailable to you. For others, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us for purposes of registration and other online activities. Kids, if you are ever unsure about anything you are seeing on this Site, ask your parent or guardian for help. See [Note To Parents](http://ww2.wizards.com/Company/Default.aspx?doc=Privacy#parents) below for more information.

To register an account with Wizards, you must provide a date of birth, first name and last name, city, country, postal code, gender, e-mail address, password and screen name.

Your personal profile (“Your Profile”) will be automatically populated with the screen name, birth date, gender, country and postal code you provided at registration. The information in Your Profile, including any information or content you voluntarily add to Your Profile such as first and last name and images you upload, will be made public by default and will not be subject to this policy, unless you set Your Profile to “Private”. To change Your Profile privacy settings, go to Your Profile page and click on “Profile” in the left navigation menu. Then click “Privacy Settings”. In this section, you may also change Your Profile information, who can view your page and activity, and who can contact you on the Site, as well as control how we communicate with you.

Your Profile will be searchable by screen name, full name, city, state/province, country, age, and postal code. You can change this by selecting “Exclude me from search results” in Privacy Settings. Please note: The photo you selected (you are not required to upload a personal photo) as your avatar and your screen name will always display on your page, posts, and in search results.

If you choose to populate Your Profile with your full name, your full name will display on Your Profile unless you set Your Profile to private as described above. Information and content you choose to make public either through Your Profile, or by posting on the Sites, are not subject to this policy.

Wizards collects information from you at other points on the Sites, as described below:

  * **Message Boards, Blogs and Social Networking**  
Wizards provides message boards, blogs and other public forums on the Sites for exchanging information and social networking. Please note that information, user content or any other materials that you post on our Sites, including any information from Your Profile that you choose to make public, will be available for any user of that service to read, and are therefore no longer private and may be disclosed without limitations as to use by a third party. If you post information, materials or other content on the Sites or other public forum, you are providing information that can be collected and used by others that you do not know for their own purposes, including the distribution of unsolicited communications.
  * **Online Stores**  
Visitors purchasing goods and services through one of our affiliate online stores will need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address.
  * **Promotions **  
To participate in some of our promotions, you may be asked to provide an e-mail address or screen name, so that we can let you know if you won a prize. For other Wizards promotions, we may request your name and home address in order to send you products or information by regular mail.
  * **Customer Service E-mails**  
By requesting your e-mail address to respond to your customer service question or comment, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you for marketing purposes. We will only use personal information (such as name, mailing address and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your name, e-mail address, and other information you provide, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments.
  * **Wizards Play Network (WPN)**  
Participants including store owners and event organizers have the opportunity to sign up with the Wizards Play Network (WPN) in order to participate in organized play events. Participants must provide certain identifiable information to be eligible to participate in these events.
  * **Resumes**  
Our Sites allow for the online submission of resumes. Personal information collected from resumes is not subject to this Privacy Policy. However, we can assure you that such information will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings.
  * **Online Surveys**  
In order to improve the user experience at our Site, we may employ online surveys for visitors to volunteer anonymous demographic information about themselves and provide us feedback about why they visit our Sites and what we can do to make them better. Information collected through these surveys is anonymous; we cannot identify who is submitting the information or tie it to other personally identifiable information a user may have provided us through another means.

Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent it is reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. If you do not want to submit personal information when requested, you will not be able to access certain areas on our Sites or take advantage of certain features of our Sites. However, you do not need to provide personal information to Wizards in order to use our Sites.

Back to top

**Who is collecting my information and how will it be used?**

Wizards collects the personal information you provide on our Sites. We may use the information you submit to our Sites to send you advertising or promotional materials, including information about new products, contests, features and enhancements, special offers and other events of interest. We may also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you and can better meet your needs. The demographic information (e.g., age and gender) you provide us is collected by Wizards and may be disclosed in aggregate to third parties. This aggregate demographic information cannot be used to personally identify you or your computer.

Third parties who fulfill Site-related services such as hosting may collect the personal information you provide on our Sites. These third parties will not use your personal information for any purpose other than to provide the Site-related services, and have agreed to maintain confidentiality, surveys, security, and integrity of your personal information.

Third parties that advertise through or serve ads on our Sites may gather non-personally identifying data about the advertisements you viewed and the Site pages that interest you through the use of cookies and clear GIFs (these technologies are described below). This information helps advertisers determine which kinds of advertisements you might prefer. Wizards’ privacy policy does not cover the policies or practices of these third parties. Visitors should consult the third parties’ privacy notices.

Back to top

**With whom does Wizards share my personal information?**

Wizards may share your information with its related entities, including its parent and sister companies.

Wizards may share your personal information with outside entities hired to assist with internal web site support operations (e.g., community operations, online product fulfillment, e-mail services, or technical support). These entities will not use your personal information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain confidentiality, surveys, security, and integrity of all the personal information they obtain from us.

Wizards also may disclose your personal information in order to fulfill a service to you. For example, if you are entering a sweepstakes or contest, we may use your personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the terms of that promotion. This means that we may share the information for prize fulfillment purposes or mail carriers. Also, if you make a purchase on one of our sites, your credit card data may have to be disclosed to an unaffiliated third party payment processing company as necessary to complete your purchase (for example, to process your credit card). In the event that such data is shared, Wizards will take all reasonable steps to ensure the applicable third parties protect the data adequately.

We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability.

Except as set forth herein, Wizards of the Coast LLC, as a subsidiary of Hasbro, Inc. does not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose personal information collected from and about its users (including children under 13) to third parties. However, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Wizards' customer information may be transferred to Wizards' successor or assign, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

**Social Media**

You also can engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter (or third-party social media plug-ins and applications). When you engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on,) from your interaction with our content.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like (1) give you exclusive content, (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our websites (and/or applications), and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly by sending you the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our privacy policy. When you provide personal information to us through an application, on our sites, or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties. 

Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

**International Transfer of Information?**

If you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information, Wizards may transfer that information to its parent, affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to:

* the use of your personally identifiable information for the uses identified above in accordance with this privacy policy; and

* the transfer of your personally identifiable information to the United States as indicated above.

Back to top

**Clear GIFs, Cookies and IP Addresses**

Clear GIFs, sometimes called "web bugs" or “pixel tags,” are file objects, usually a graphic image such as a transparent one pixel-by-one pixel GIF (Graphics Interchange Format, one of the two most common file formats for images on the Web), that are placed on a Web page or in an e-mail message to monitor user behavior. The GIF tells us the IP address of the computer that fetched our page, the URL of the page the GIF is on, the time the page was viewed, the type of browser used, and it can also identify a previously set cookie value. This anonymous information is returned by the clear GIF to Wizards and we use this information to accurately count visitors across our web sites and understand how they navigate and use our network of web sites. Wizards does not combine information gathered through clear GIFs with your personal information.

Wizards uses "cookies" to enhance your experience at our Sites. Cookies are pieces of information that we place on your computer to help us accurately understand how many consumers are visiting a particular site, how often they visit that site and what content they are most interested in viewing. For example, a cookie will allow us to remember certain things based on your Internet Protocol or "IP" address (an IP address is the string of numbers that identifies each sender or receiver of information that is sent across the Internet), such as the time and duration of your visits, how you navigated through our content and where you exited a particular site.

Wizards' web sites collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our web sites. When visitors request pages on one of our web sites, our servers log the visitors' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our community rules Code of Conduct or posted Legal Notice, or to protect our services, web sites, customers, or others.

Back to top

**Log Files**

Other information passively collected by Wizards is in the form of logs -- files that record web site activity and gather statistics about web users' browsing habits. These entries are generated anonymously, and help Wizards determine (among other things) how many and how often users have visited our web sites, which pages they've visited, and other similar data. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you.

Back to top

**Linking to third party sites**

To provide relevant information not found on our Sites and to facilitate online shopping, Wizards may provide links from our Sites to third party web sites. We encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information..

Back to top

**Opt-out**

If you do not want Wizards to send you e-mail or regular mail about our products and/or services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or at the time of information collection. If you are receiving e-mails or regular mail and at a later date you choose to opt-out and have your name removed from Wizards' e-mail list, you can do so by using the link included with a Wizards e-mail or by contacting customer service.

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

Back to top

**Safeguarding your personal information**

Wizards will only collect personal information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will take appropriate steps to ensure the security and integrity of any information you provide to us. Any information provided to us is housed in a PCI-certified secure datacenter, accessible by limited Wizards personnel secured with passkeys and under 24-hour video surveillance. Wizards uses Secure Sockets Layering, an industry-standard protocol for certain of your transmissions to us, in order to encrypt the personal information that you send to us through account registration and payment processes. We store your information in an encrypted format.

Back to top

**Review, update and removal of personal information**

If you have registered with our site, you may at any time review and/or update the contact information we have for you or inform us that you want us to remove your information from our database by contacting customer service. Please be sure to include in your message the name of the feature for which you registered and the e-mail address you used to register so that we can verify your request.

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

Back to top

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Wizards who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share our customer’s personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

To make such a request, contact customer service:

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

Back to top

**Questions and Complaints**

Any questions or complaints about Wizards or this privacy statement can be addressed by contacting Customer Service:

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

We reserve the right to change this statement at any time, so visit this page from time to time to check for changes. For additional information about our web sites, please see our Terms and Conditions of Use.

Back to top

###  NOTE TO PARENTS

Wizards has developed its web sites to be an enjoyable experience for children (and adults) of all ages. Wizards recognizes that some younger children may not understand some of the information contained on the web sites or how the web sites operate. That is the purpose of the Privacy Statement. Please discuss this statement with your children so that they will better understand how to use the web sites and the information they may be asked to provide. Wizards strongly believes that providing its visitors with accurate and adequate notice about the web sites will lead to informed choices and decisions about how to use the web sites, as well as protect its users' privacy. If you have any questions or comments about our policy, please contact us using the Contact Information provided below. For all other issues, please contact [Wizards Customer Service](http://wizards.custhelp.com/).

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

Back to top

**Teenagers (Ages 13-17)**

Wizards may collect personal information from users over 13 and under 18 ("teenager"). When a web site user in this age category submits personal information, Wizards may request a parent or guardian's e-mail address to notify the parent or guardian of the teenager's activity. Personal information collected from these visitors is subject to the policies set forth above..

Back to top

**Children Under 13**

**Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information **

Wizards may collect and store personal information about children under 13 ("children" or "child") if it is submitted by way of our registration form and with the parent's or legal guardian’s verifiable consent. To determine who is younger than 13 years old and whether parental consent is required, we ask all users who wish to register to submit their date of birth. Those users that indicate they are under 13 years of age are directed to a Parental Consent Form. The Parental Consent Form is available for viewing [here](https://accounts.wizards.com/CoppaForm.htm), and it must be signed and returned to Wizards by mail or fax, before we will collect information from users who have indicated they are under 13.

If given verifiable permission from a parent or legal guardian, Wizards may collect and store the following types of personal information about a child under 13: name, e-mail address, mailing address, parent's or legal guardian's name, and parent's or legal guardian's email address. Wizards may also collect demographic information about a child such as the child's date of birth, gender, and other preferences; and, combine such information with the child's personal information. Wizards will only collect this information if it is voluntarily submitted to us by the child or parent/ legal guardian and provided with the parent's or legal guardian’s signed permission. We do not gather personal information about a child through the use of passive collection mechanisms such as cookies. For more information on how we use cookies and other information collection tools, please see our section on cookies (provided above).

The information that a child provides on his/her registration form may be used to: (a) allow the child to participate in activities on our web sites (e.g., contests); and, (b) allow us to send the child promotional materials, including information about new products, contests, features and enhancements, special offers, and other events of interest.

Wizards may share kids' personal information with outside entities hired to assist with internal website support operations (e.g., online product fulfillment, e-mail services, or technical support). These entities will not use kids' personal information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain confidentiality, surveys, security, and integrity of all the personal information they obtain from us.

We may also use the information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so that we can constantly improve the products and services we provide our visitors and to better meet their needs.

Please note that we are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity - like contests - on the child's disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. To read about the steps Wizards takes to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of children's personal information, please see our section on "Safeguarding your personal information" (above).

In some instances, certain portions of our web sites (e.g., electronic postcards) will allow children under 13 to submit personal information such as their e-mail addresses without first obtaining their parents' or legal guardians’ consent. Such portions of our web sites operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent under the law.

Other areas of our web sites will facilitate a child’s participation in our Community features such as forums, wikis, and blogs, as well as creation of a profile. Your child’s participation may result in public disclosure of the personal information he or she posts through these features. We will take all reasonable measures to delete any personal information of a child posted through our Community features if and when such information is discovered.

Back to top

**Disclosure of Children's Personal Information**

Wizards may share children's personal information with outside entities hired to assist with internal web site support operations (e.g., community operations, online product fulfillment, e-mail services, or technical support). These web sites will not use this personal information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain confidentiality, surveys, security, and integrity of all the personal information they obtain from us.

We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability.

Wizards, as a subsidiary of Hasbro, Inc. does not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose personal information collected from and about its users (including children under 13) to third parties. However, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Wizards' customer information may be transferred to Wizards' successor or assign, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

Back to top

**Safeguarding Children's Personal Information**

Wizards will only collect personal information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will take appropriate steps to ensure the security and integrity of any information your child provides to us. Any information provided to us is housed in a secure datacenter, accessible by limited Wizards personnel.

Back to top

**Notification of Updates to Privacy Policy**

Changes to the privacy policy will be made to this page. We may also notify customers via email and/or other means, in our discretion.

Back to top

**Parental Access**

A parent who has already given Wizards permission to collect and use his or her child’s personal information can, at any time review, correct, or have deleted the child's personal information or discontinue further collection and use of the child's personal information. To do so, please contact us using the contact information below and be sure to include the following:

  * Your child's name and e-mail address
  * Your name and e-mail address
  * The name of the feature for which your child is registered

We will be happy to honor your request.

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

Back to top

**Wizards Contact Information**

Any personal information that a child provides to our web sites for purposes of registration is collected by Wizards. Wizards contact information is as follows:

Wizards contact options:

**Write to us at:** Wizards of the Coast  
ATTN: Game Support  
P.O. Box 707  
Renton, WA 98057-0707

**Call us:** Monday through Friday, from 9 am to 6 pm Pacific Time, and also on weekends from 10 am to 4 pm Pacific Time:  
US/Canada: (800) 324-6496  
Other countries: (425) 204-8069

**Submit a help request** (requires creating an account or signing in to your account): <http://wizards.custhelp.com/>

[webregistration@wizards.com](mailto:webregistration@wizards.com)Wizards is a licensee of the ESRB’s Privacy Online Program. If you believe that we have not properly responded to your inquiry, you may also contact ESRB Privacy Online at <http://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.jsp>

ESRB  
Attn.: Director, Privacy Online  
317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10017  

Back to top
